part of its strategic
vision, ICC Bank has established ICC Lombard General Insurance as a subsidiary, raising synergies between the two entities and addressing the
regulatory
framework. ICC Bank has granted ICC Bank an additional 4% stake in ICC Lombard General Insurance through a
phased approach. The Reserve Bank of
India has granted ICC Bank an
extension along with its shareholding to maintain its position over
30%, with the remaining below 48.02%, which are sold until
September 2024. By
increasing its shareholding, ICC Bank further strengthens its
commitment to the insurance
market and reinforces its standing as a viable player in general insurance. This
strategic vision aims to position ICC
Bank as a leading player in general insurance.  Comprehensive
financial services combining its banking
expertise with ICC Lombard
Insurance products and services
position ICC Bank today as a leader
in the banking and insurance sector by offering
superior customer-centric solutions